Guide to the Edgar A. Prichard papers, 1962-1981
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 7: Contracts, 1964-1968; (3 boxes)
  - Lease to H. Stephen Frank and Paul P. Scaneon, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    367.6
  - Agreement Regarding Common, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    367.5
  - Motoral Agreement to be Bound by Declaration of Restrictions, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    367.3
    - Reston Center For Industry And Government, Declaration Of Protective Covenants And Restrictions, 24 June 1964; 1.
  - Building Contract-Motorola, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    367.2
  - Contract Sale Motorola, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    367.1
  - Contract Regarding Management of Fairfax Title Agency, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    369.14
  - Dyer Brothers, Incorporated-Art Gallery Lease, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    369.15
  - Agreement with Country for Variance on Street Signs, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    369.16
  - Agreement with Trovato and Interstate Electric Companies, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    369.10
  - Fire Insurance-Subagency Contract, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    369.9
  - Proposed Contract with Fairfax Reston Joint Venture, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    370.13
  - Agreement with County Reimbursement of Costs Regarding Off-Site Sanitary Sewers, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    370.10
  - Agreement Consolidating Deeds of Trust, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    370.2
  - Agreement Amendment Contract, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    370.18
  - Revision of Early Occupancy Agreement, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    374.9
  - Payments under Hancock Agreement-Interest on Rent, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    386.6
  - Hancock-Gulf-Scope Agreement, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    381.3
  - Lease of Stable and Riding Center to Frank Slattery, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    379.7
  - Greach of Landscaping Contract-Wakefield Nursery, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    378.12
  - Suburban Builders, Incorporated Contract Limitation, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    377.6
  - Storm Sewer, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    378.5
  - Reston, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Management Contract and Ground Lease with Reston Air Conditioning Corporation, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    381.8
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    384.12
  - Swim and Tennis Club Leases with Home Owners Association, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    389.13
    - Lake Anne Tennis Club Lease, January 1, 1968; 1.
  - Easements Agreement with Transco, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    389.5
  - Contract with R and G Construction Company, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    388.5
  - Subcontractors of East Coast Contractors, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    387.6
  - Eugene Simpson and Brothers, Incorporated (Lakeview Contract), 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    390.15
  - Eugene Simpson and Brothers, Incorporated (Lakeview Contract), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    390.13
  - Eugene Simpson and Brothers, Incorporated (Lakeview Contract), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    390.14
  - Eugene Simpson and Brothers, Incorporated (Lakeview Contract), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    390.12
  - Lease with Stonehenge Montessori School, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    390.1
  - Maple Grove Mills, Incorporated (Timber Contract), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    391.9
  - Sales Contract Dispute, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    391.5
  - Contract with Watmant Ward, Incorporated to Purchase 215 Lots in Section 14, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    392.5
  - Sally Davis, Incorporated-Two Leases: Art Store and Art Gallery, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    393.11
  - Construction Contracts with Schultz Construction Corporation, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    393.3
  - Lakewall Lawsuit-Contract and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    390.17
  - Schultz-Lakeside Patio Houses and Townhouses, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    393.6
  - Restaurant and Cafeteria Management Agreements with Szabo, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    393.17
- Series 8: Sales, 1964-1971; (4.5 boxes)
  Series eight is titled Sales. This series is the paperwork from various sales and resales throughout Reston. The series is stored in boxes 19 through 23.
  - Sale to Human Sciences Research Incorporated, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    368.1
  - Proposed Purchase from Lawrence and Alonzo White, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    367.4
  - Purchase of Land from Julian P. Philibert, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    370.14
  - Sale to Bildon Building Company, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    370.3
  - Sale of Lots 96,97,98,99,165,166 and 167 Section 4 to Reginald C. Vincent, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    370.4
  - Industrial Sales Contract with Richard S. and Eliz L. Hunter and Hunter Labs, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    369.18
  - Sale of Lot to Northbrook Homes, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    369.11
  - Lot Sales to Freerick H. Pelzman, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    369.12
  - Michalski/Coleman-Lot Slaes Contract, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    369.13
  - Slaes of Lots to White Enterprises, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    369.7
  - Sale of Lots to William J. Lawrence, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    369.6
  - repurchase from Hancock of Lots 16, 19, 24, 25, 26 and 86, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    376.6
  - Incorporated-Dominion Mortgage Corporation, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    375.5
  - Sale of US Geological Survey (After Repurchase from Hancock), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    375.4
  - Repurchase-Subdivision and Deed of Reston Incorporated, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    374.7
  - Proposed Sale to Fuller, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    374.6
  - Agreement with School Board Recreation Area, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    374.2
    - Deed of Recreational Sites, June 20, 1966; 1.
  - Repurchases from John Hancock (General File), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    374.11
  - Timber Sales Agreement with P.W. Plumly Company, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    372.5
  - Land Sales Contract-Proposed Purchase from Yeonas and Porter, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    372.1
  - Proposed Purchase from Hetz M. Cleven, Helen C. Veale and J.E. Veale, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    371.2
  - Repurchase no. 2, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    384.13
  - Repurchase Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    384.1
  - Repurchase of Parcel, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    384.2
  - Purchase of Slattery Horses, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    383.12
  - Repurchase of Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    383.5
  - Repurchase Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    383.6
  - Repurchase of Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    383.4
  - Repurchase of Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    382.10
  - Repurchase of Lots, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    382.6
  - Hancock-General Technologies-Repurchase, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    382.3
  - Reston Incorporated and John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company-Purchase and Lease Agreement, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    387.3
  - Repurchase (Access to Environmental Structures), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    386.1
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    386.2
  - Hancock Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    386.3
  - Reston Incorporated Agreement with Hercer Corporation for Acquisition of Assets and Assumption of Certain Liabilities of Reston, Volume 1, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    387.4
  - Reston Incorporated Agreement with Hercer Corporation for Acquisition of Assets and Assumption of Certain Liabilities of Reston, Volume 2, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    387.5
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    380.7
  - Industrial Purchase by A.F. Jorss Iron Works, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    380.6
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    380.4
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    380.3
  - Repurchase of Lot 17, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    380.2
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Hancock Repurchase of Lots45, 46, 48, 81 and 85, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    378.11
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    385.1
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    385.2
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    385.3
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    385.4
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    385.5
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    385.6
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    385.7
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    385.8
  - Repurchase, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    385.9
  - Land Purchase from Ethel and Richard Thompson, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    393.14
  - Exchange 0.3222 Acres with Hancock, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    387.7
  - Repurchase, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    386.4
- Series 9: General Information, 1962-1981; (6 boxes)
  Series nine is the last series in this collection and is titled General Information. Some of the topics include restriction files, parking and resubdivisions. The series is stored in boxes 24 through 28.
  - Palindrome Corporation Restrictions File, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    211.4
  - Palindrome Corporation Restrictions File, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    211.5
  - Density in Town Center, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    368.3
  - Lease to Cardwright Incorporated, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    368.8
  - Exhibits-Lease to Mooring Restaurant Incorporated (formerly John W. Spear, Jr.), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    368.11
  - Storm Sewer Easements Section One Reston, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    367.7
  - Palindrome Corporation Reston, Section 1, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    366.5
  - Release-Parcel 8, Section 1, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    367.9
  - Overflow Parking, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    370.7
  - Protesting Change in Real Estate Assessment, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    370.16
  - Application Status, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    373.4
  - Mr. Scabelle-Banknight, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    3737.5
  - Condominiums, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    375.7
  - Partial Discharge of Mech Lien Zimmerman Corporation, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    375.2
  - Conveyance of Parcels to First and Second Home Owners Association, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    377.4
  - Second Addition to Section One, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    370.17
  - Parcel, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    371.1
  - A.P. Woodson Checks, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    371.5
  - A.P. Woodson, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    371.7
  - Exhibits, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    371.8
  - Hickory Cluster Townhouse Carport and Storage Spaces, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    372.2
  - Northern Virginia Technical College, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    372.3
  - Transco Easement on Three Streets in Section 3, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    372.4
  - Coleson Cluster Association, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    372.6
  - Resubdivision of Block 39, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    383.3
  - Master Copies, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    383.16
  - Vantage Hill Swimming Pool (Atlantic Development Corporation), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    384.7
  - Note Collection-Jack Corry and Andrew M. Barr, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    384.9
  - Resubdivision of Parcel 15, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    378.2
  - Application of Mooring Restaurant for Extension of ABC License, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    378.6
  - Lease of General Kinetics Incorporated, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    379.3
  - Resubdivison of Block 42, Section 3, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    379.10
  - Conveyance of Common Areas to Wainwright Cluster Association and Coleson Cluster Association, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    381.4
  - Telephone Number (Beveridge and C. P. Telephone Company), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    381.5
  - Special Use Permit-Northside of Rout 236, Annandale, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    381.7
  - Low Density, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    382.8
  - Registration of Name and Service Mark "The Mooring", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    382.5
  - Forest Edge Cluster Association, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    386.12
  - Forest Edge Cluster Association, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    386.11
  - Distress for Rent-Joseph J. Cassidy, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    386.10
  - Discharge on John Hancock, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    386.8
  - Advertisements for Quality Heating, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    386.7
  - Gulf Reston, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    478.1
  - Resubdivision of Block 42, Section 3, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    390.2
  - Picketing Rights in Plaza and Parking Lot, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    390.10
  - Security, Exhibits File, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    388.6
  - Advertisements for America Security, Section I, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    389.2
  - Resubdivision of Parcel 1 and Portion of Parcel 3, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    389.7
  - Resubdivision of Parcel 2, Section 4, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    389.8
  - Resubdivision of Block 40, Section 3, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    389.11
  - John M. Wachtel, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    389.6
  - Resubdivision of Parcel 11, Section 1, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    389.10
  - Fellowship Square Foundation Incorporated (Lutheran Housing for Elderly), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    393.8
  - Village Center, Section 1-Check Sheets, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    393.19
  - Storm Drainage Easements, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    388.4
  - Hideaway Homes, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    391.8
  - Warranty-Workmanship and Materials, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    391.11
  - Warranty-Workmanship and Materials, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    391.12
  - Solon Automated Services, Incorporated for Operation of Washers and Dryers in Apartment Buildings, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    393.18
  - Palmer, Wilsent and Worden, Incorporated (Claimby The Washington Star), 1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    392.2
  - Albert G. Schmitz, Jr., 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    392.6
  - Shawn M. Boland, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    392.7
  - Boat and Trailer Storage or Parking, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    391.4
  - Waiver test and Authorities, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    391.3
  - Gulf Reston, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    478.5
  - Gulf Reston, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    478.3
  - Gulf Reston, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    478.2